# **MARK DANIEL JAIME**

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

I have I year experience as front end developer and 6 months as web designer. I have a great passion in web development, interested in learning new technologies. Willing to be train. Capable to work as a team or solo with minimum supervision.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Colegio de San Juan de Letran Calamba

Bachelor in Information Technology , 2011-2015

#### CONTACT

#### Phone:

+639165087706

#### **Email:**

markdjaime@gmail.com

#### Web:

markakoyun.github.io /markjaime/

#### Home:

Cabuyao, Laguna

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DESIGNER**

Personiv | Nov 2016 - April 2017

- Worked on a team as web designer.
- Designed and developed a website depending on the specification of our client in US.
- Maintained and modified client site.
- Optimized client site.

#### FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

88DB PHILIPPINES INC. | Sep 2015 - July 2016

- Worked as the main front end developer on a team.
- Worked with back end developer in developing web application.
- Converted psd design mockups into responsive html.
- Maintained company portal site.
- Maintained client site throught CMS and hardcoding

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML/HTML5 • •
  - Bootstrap
- ••••

- CSS/CSS3
- ••••
- Responsive
- ••••

- JavaScript
- ••••
- SASS
- ••••

- jQuery
- ••••
- Photoshop

## OTHER TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Familiarity with CMS such as Wordpress and basic understanding on creating a theme from scratch.
- Good understanding of using GIT and GitHub.
- Knowledge with package manager such as Bower.
- Familiarity with a task runner for development such as Gulp.
- Good understanding of other CSS Frameworks.
- Basic understanding of RESTful API, Json and Ajax.